http://www.tigerdroppings.com/site-matters/privacy-policy/35032360/

Privacy  •  Advertising  •  Contact  •  Terms
Copyright @2020 TigerDroppings.com. All rights reserved.
HomeForumsRecruitingPick'emTD Store...LSU Football ScheduleLinks PageMember ListHelp ForumGuidelines/FAQ
X
Forums
Sign In|Register
Sign InRegisterHomeForumsTrending TopicsTD StoreLSU NewsSports LiteSECRant.comPick'emLSU Football ScheduleRecruiting TrackerMore LinksCustomizeMy ForumsTrendingQuick Links:Tiger Rant•LSU Recruiting•O-T Lounge•Politics•Election 2020•More Sports•Coaching Changes•SEC Rant•Saints•Home/Garden•Outdoors•Movie/TV•Food/Drink•Money•Tech•Music•Travel•TD Help...My ForumsTiger RantLSU RecruitingSEC RantSaints TalkPelicans TalkMore Sports BoardCoaching ChangesFantasy SportsGolf BoardSoccer BoardO-T LoungeTech BoardHome/Garden BoardOutdoor BoardHealth/Fitness BoardMovie/TV BoardBook BoardMusic BoardPolitical TalkElection 2020Money TalkFark BoardGaming BoardTravel BoardFood/Drink BoardTicket ExchangeTD Help BoardCustomize My ForumsView All Forums Topic Sort OptionsTrending TopicsRecent TopicsActive Topics
Privacy Policyby ChickenAugust 2, 2012Share on FacebookShare on Twitter0Your privacy is important to us. To protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the ways your information is collected and used.
This notice applies to all information collected from users or submitted by users on our website. If you are a user of our website, including those users in the European Union Area , your continued use of the website signifies your consent to the information collection, use of cookies, our privacy policy and our terms of use.
Users in California and the European Union Area who do not consent to the information collection noted below, should discontinue use of our website until we are able to provide an opt-in and opt-out mechanism relating to the collection of personal information.
Personal information collected by us includes:
* Email Address (submitted by users who register for our website)
* IP Address (collected for all registered users)
We do not sell your data that we collect, or share your email address or IP address with outside parties, unless we are required to do so by a valid court order. The information submitted by you or collected by us is used by the moderators of the website to facilitate quality control and to communicate with you as necessary.
In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures intended to safeguard the information we collect online.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may collect and use, among other data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, and the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over by you.
During your visits to this and other websites, this information may be used
to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit
networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Google is one of the third-parties with which we work. Google serves ads and collects certain user and site information. To learn more about how Google uses this information, please click on the following link:
https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at tigerdroppings@gmail.com.Filed Under: Site Matters Popular Stories35 LSU RB Chris Curry Sends Out Positive Message To Tiger NationLove the attitude.29 Ed Orgeron Comments On The Arik Gilbert SituationHere's the latest.38 LSU Fans Will Love This Tweet From Offensive Lineman Ed IngramHe's locked in.24 Ed Orgeron Comments On BJ Ojulari's StatusThe talented freshman is HS teammates with Arik Gilbert.14 Punter Zach Von Rosenberg Was Asked About The Team Morale On TuesdayKeep fighting.
LATEST HEADLINES Follow TD on Facebook and Twitter Contact Us Privacy Policy Advertising Info Contact Us Advertising Info Privacy Policy Posting Guidelines Contact Us Privacy Policy
Follow TigerDroppings for LSU Football NewsFollow us on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram to get the latest updates on LSU Football and Recruiting.Facebook•Twitter•Instagram
Advertising Info
•
Privacy Policy
•
Contact Us
•
Terms
© 2020 TigerDroppings.com.
All Rights Reserved
